One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
‫الثروة والصيت والقوة،‬
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
‫الرجل الذي نال كل ما في هذا العالم، ملك القراصنة غولد روجر‬
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
‫أجَّج قوله قبيل موته اندفاع الناس إلى البحار‬
You want my treasure?
‫كنزي؟ إنه لكم إن أردتموه‬
Find it!
‫ابحثوا عنه، تركت كلَّ شيءٍ في ذلك المكان!‬
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
‫شدّ الرجال رحالهم نحو الغراند لاين مطاردين أحلامهم‬
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
‫العالم الآن يعيش عصر القراصنة العظيم‬
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
‫أحلامنا جمعناها فيما بيننا‬
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
‫قاصدين البحث عما نريد الحصول عليه‬
One Piece! ONE PIECE
‫ون بيس‬
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
‫ما كانت البوصلة لتأتي لنا سوى بالتأخير‬
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
‫نمضي في طريقنا بهمة المشاعر المشتعلة‬
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
‫وخريطة الكنز القديمة التي يعلوها التراب‬
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
‫لن تكون محض قصة خرافية إن تبينا صحتها‬
When the world's got you down,
‫وإن هبت بداخلك عواصف هوجاء‬
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
‫فتمايل على إيقاع الآخرين حولك‬
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
‫وتجاهل وجودها‬
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
‫أحلامنا جمعناها فيما بيننا‬
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
‫قاصدين البحث عما نريد الحصول عليه‬
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
‫عملة أحفظها في جيبي‬
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
‫وهل تريد أن تكون صديقي؟‬
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
‫نحن، نحن نخوض مغامرة‬
WE ARE!
‫نحن‬
Gin!
‫غين!‬
No matter how incredible he was in the past, he's just a cook now.
‫لا تهم قوّته في الماضي فما هو إلا طباخٌ الآن‬
Blowing his brains out would be easy.
‫سهلٌ تفجير رأسه.‬
You want to save this man, right, Sanji?
‫ألا تريد إنقاذ هذا الرجل يا سانجي-سان؟‬
Then please... leave this ship without a fight.
‫غادر السفينة دون قتال رجاءً.‬
I don't want to kill you.
‫لا أريد قتلك.‬
Leave this ship?
‫أغادر السفينة؟‬
Piss off!
‫مُحال!‬
You look ridiculous, you old fart.
‫كم تبدو غبيًا أيها العجوز اللعين.‬
What kind of example are you setting for the fighting cooks?
‫على حالتك هذه، لن تُعدّ قدوة حسنة للطباخين المقاتلين‬
I don't need a lecture from a little eggplant.
‫لا أحتاج لمحاضرة من شقي صغير‬
Who are you calling "little eggplant," old fart?!
‫من الشقي الصغير أيها الوغد؟‬
Quit treating me like a kid already!
‫كفاك معاملتي طفلًا!‬
Sanji, you son of a...
‫يا لسانجي...‬
He's not turning his back on the head chef, is he?
‫لن يتخلى عن المالك، صحيح؟‬
Gin!
‫غين!‬
Point that gun at me instead.
‫وجِّه ذلك المسدس نحوي‬
Are you stupid?! You're gonna die!
‫أأنت أحمق؟ ستموت‬
I might.
‫ربما...‬
Sanji, why...?
‫سانجي-سان... لماذا؟‬
If you're that desperate to die, I will give you a gentleman's death.
‫إن كنتَ ترغب الموت بشدة فسأقتلك بلباقة...‬
But you'll need to hold still, or else we'll blow the proprietor's head off.
‫لا تتحرك إن كنتَ لا تريد أن يُفجر رأس مالك مطعمكم‬
Pristine Pearl...
‫تشو تينن بيرل بريزنت‬ ‫هدية اللآلئ الطبيعية القصوى‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي!‬
Why didn't you dodge that?!
‫لماذا لم تتفاداه؟!‬
If I did, that damn lackey would pull the trigger.
‫لضغط التابع الوغد على الزناد إن تفاديتها‬
Why?
‫لماذا؟‬
If you leave this restaurant, then everyone lives!
‫إن تركتَ هذا المطعم، فسينجو الجميع‬
It's a no-brainer!
‫هذا بديهي!‬
This restaurant is his treasure!
‫المطعم هو كنز ذلك العجوز اللعين!‬
It's my fault the old fart lost everything...
‫سلبتُ العجوز اللعين كل شيء...‬
His power...
‫قوته...‬
His dream...
‫حلمه...‬
So I've decided...
‫لذلك...‬
I won't let that old fart lose anything else!
‫لا أريد أن يخسر هذا العجوز اللعين شيئًا آخر!‬
Sanji! Watch out!
‫انتبه يا سانجي!‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي!‬
The All Blue?
‫الأزرق الكامل؟‬
Yeah!
‫نعم!‬
It's a legendary sea.
‫إنه بحر أسطوري‬
It's definitely out there somewhere!
‫لا بُدّ أنه موجود في مكانٍ ما!‬
Because of a Dream
‫لأن الأحلام موجودة‬
Don't be silly!
‫كفاكَ سخافةً‬
The Orbit A Passenger Ship
‫الأوربت، سفينة ركاب‬
I mean, there is a legend like that...
‫رغم أن لهذه الأسطورة وجود فعلًا...‬
We're seafaring cooks, after all,
‫حسنٌ... نحن طباخو سُفن‬
so we've all dreamed of that sea at one point.
‫فقد حلمنا جميعًا بهذا البحر يومًا‬
Right?
‫أليس كذلك؟!‬
Sanji (9 Years Ago) Cook's Apprentice Passenger Ship
‫سانجي (قبل تسع سنوات)‬ ‫سفينة الركاب‬ ‫طباخ متدرب‬
I'll definitely find that sea someday!
‫سأجد هذا البحر يومًا حتمًا!‬
You say you'll find it, but...
‫تقول أنك ستجده، لكن...‬
For starters, do you even know what kind of place the All Blue is?
‫أتعلم أيُّ الأماكن هو الأزرق الكامل أساسًا؟‬
Of course I do! I'm not an idiot!
‫أكيد، لا تحسبني جاهلًا!‬
The East Blue, West Blue, North Blue, and South Blue...
‫الأزرق الشرقي والأزرق الغربي والأزرق الشمالي والأزرق الجنوبي...‬
A sea where fish from all four seas live...
‫إنه بحر يجمع أسماكًا من هاته البحار...‬
That's the All Blue.
‫هذا هو الأزرق الكامل‬
To seafaring cooks, it's an irresistible paradise!
‫فإنه جنة لا تُقاوم بالنسبة لطبّاخي السفن‬
That's my dream!
‫هذا حلمي!‬
That's the place!
‫فعلًا ستجد طعامًا بحريًّا من كل العالم في ذلك البحر‬
Any cook would be itching to show their skills there!
‫ستغمر الحماسة الطابخين لإظهار مهاراتهم!‬
Yeah.
‫نعم.‬
It's worth risking your life to look for that sea.
‫إنه أمر يستحق المرء المخاطرة بحياته من أجله‬
That is, if such a sea exists...
‫هذا إن وُجد بحر كهذا فعلًا...‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
There's no way a miracle sea like the All Blue could exist.
‫مستحيل لبحرٍ معجزة كالأزرق الكامل أن يوجد فعلًا...‬
It's obvious when you think about it.
‫الأمر واضح إن فكرتَ فيه قليلًا...‬
Some daydreaming cook must have told it as a tall tale.
‫على الأرجح أنه كذبة كبيرة من طباخ حالم...‬
Now, enough with the silly stories.
‫والآن، كفانا من الحكايات السخيفة‬
Go bus the tables, Sanji.
‫اجمع الأطباق يا سانجي‬
What a waste to leave so much food...
‫يا للخسارة، سيضيع طعام كثير...‬
They barely touched this one.
‫بالكاد لمسوا هذا الطبق.‬
I was sure they'd like it.
‫كنتُ واثقًا أنهم سيحبونه.‬
Customers these days sure are spoiled.
‫زبائن هذه الأيام مدللون حقًّا.‬
You need to stop eating the customers' leftovers.
‫كفاكم عن أكل بقايا الزبائن‬
Some of the food I threw out earlier looked gross.
‫رميتُ الطعام الذي بدا فاسدًا قبل قليل‬
You're still only half a cook if you say things like that.
‫يُظهر قول أشياء كهذه أنك ما زلت في منتصف طريقك طباخًا‬
Don't forget we're seafaring cooks.
‫لا تنسَ أننا طباخو سُفن‬
The sea is an unpredictable place, so it's best not to waste food.
‫البحر مكان لا يمكن التنبؤ به، لذا من الأفضل ألا نضيّع الطعام‬
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
‫لمَ لا تتناول بعضه أيضًا؟‬
I don't want it!
‫لا أريد!‬
Everyone, calm down! Please calm down!
‫حافظوا على هدوئكم، اهدؤوا رجاءً!‬
Pirates!
‫قراصنة!‬
Pirates?!
‫قراصنة؟‬
That ship belongs to...
‫تلك السفينة...‬
the Cook Pirates!
‫لقراصنة الطباخون، سفينة الساق الحمراء زيف!‬
Looks like they came back from the Grand Line!
‫إذًا فقد عادوا من الغراند لاين!‬
"Red Leg" Zeff Cook Pirates
‫زيف الساق الحمراء‬ ‫قراصنة الطباخون‬
You're the pirate captain Red Leg Zeff I presume?
‫أظنك القبطان زيف الساق الحمراء،‬
How may I assist you?
‫كيف أساعدك؟‬
Plunder!
‫انهبوا!‬
Steal all their valuables!
‫اسلبوهم كل أغراضهم الثمينة!‬
Dammit! I can't die here...
‫سُحقًا، لن أُقتل!‬
These scumbags can't kill me!
‫لن أُقتل على يد أوغاد مثلهم!‬
Whoa!
‫ما هذا؟‬
What's with this brat?
‫ما قصة هذا الفتى؟‬
Hey, punk. It's dangerous to swing something like that around.
‫يا فتى، لا تلوح بأشياء خطرة كهذه‬
Look. Blood. I'm so injured.
‫أنا أنزف، إنها إصابة خطيرة‬
Shut up! I'm not gonna be killed by bastards like you!
‫اخرسا، لن أُقتل على يد أوغاد مثلكم!‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي!‬
Stop it! Don't fight back!
‫توقف، لا تقاتلهم!‬
That kid's asking for it! Just hurry up and kill him!
‫أرى أنه لا يهاب الموت، عجّلوا بقتله‬
I don't want to die!
‫لا أريد الموت!‬
If I am gonna die, I'd like to take a few of you bastards out first!
‫إن كنتُ سأُقتل على يدكم، عليّ قتل بعضكم أولًا!‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي!‬
Man, you did it, Captain.
‫فعلتَها أيها القبطان‬
Always so merciless.
‫لا رحمة عندك‬
I'm not gonna die...!
‫لن أموت!‬
I...
‫أنا...‬
Someday... I will find the All Blue!
‫سأجد الأزرق الكامل يومًا!‬
He said "All Blue"!
‫قال الأزرق الكامل!‬
That's one hell of a goal!
‫يا له من حلم طموح!‬
Captain, tell him how we couldn't even find it in the Grand Line.
‫أخبره أيها القبطان... أن ذلك ليس موجودًا حتى في الغراند لاين‬
That idiot! He's still spouting that nonsense...
‫ذلك الغبي، ما زال يردد ذلك الهراء...‬
I'm not gonna be killed by some damn pirates in a place like this!
‫لن أُقتل على يد قراصنة أوغاد في مكان كهذا!‬
Captain! Let's withdraw!
‫لننسحب أيها القبطان!‬
This storm is taking a turn for the worse!
‫إن العاصفة أشدّ ممَّا حسبنا!‬
That decides it, men!
‫يا رجال،‬
Hurry and load the treasure onto our ship!
‫أسرعوا واحملوا الكنز للسفينة!‬
We're withdrawing!
‫سننسحب!‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي!‬
Captain!
‫أيها القبطان!‬
That damn kid!
‫شقي لعين!‬
Why'd he do that just for a little brat?!
‫لمَ قد تفعل هذا من أجل ذلك الشقي؟!‬
Finally awake, little eggplant?
‫أراك استيقظتَ أخيرًا أيها الشقي‬
You're quite lucky.
‫أنت محظوظ جدًا‬
Pirat–
‫–أيها القر‬
Figures you can't move.
‫مستحيلٌ أن تستطيع الحركة!‬
You think you can just shrug off a kick from me?
‫فتلك ركلاتي أنا التي تلقيتَها‬
So the ships...?
‫ماذا عن السفن؟‬
Who knows? The sea was very rough.
‫لا أعلم... كان البحر هائجًا‬
It's likely they were completely destroyed.
‫لن أتفاجأ إن دُمرت كاملةً‬
We're the only ones who washed up here...
‫نحن الوحيدان اللذان انتهى بنا المطاف هنا‬
This rocky mound has neither fruits nor animals.
‫لا يوجد حيوانات أو فاكهة على هذا الجبل الصخري‬
Sure, there are fish in the sea below,
‫على الأقل هناك سمك في البحر،‬
but the waves have curved the rock inwards,
‫لكن بسبب نحت الأمواج لهذه الصخرة،‬
which sadly means going down is a one-way trip.
‫لن نتمكن من الصعود ثانية إن نزلنا، أليسَ هذا يُبكي؟‬
All of this is your fault!
‫هذا خطؤك كاملًا!‬
I'll kill you!
‫سأقتلك!‬
Complain all you like.
‫واصل الشكوى‬
We have no choice but to wait for help.
‫ما بيدنا حيلة سوى انتظار مساعَدة‬
But if no one comes, we'll just dry up and become skeletons.
‫إن لم يأتِ أحد فسنجف ونتحول لهيكلين عظميين‬
I'll become...
‫أنا، هيكل عظمي...؟‬
That bag over there is your share.
‫حصتك في ذلك الكيس هناك‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
It's food that luckily washed up here.
‫ذلك هو الطعام الذي انجرف معنا لحسن الحظ‬
With the portions you're used to, it'll only last you five days.
‫إنها مؤونة خمسة أيام تقريبًا إن أكلتَ باعتدال‬
Use your head and ration your food.
‫استعمل عقلك وكل‬
It's a good thing we're both cooks.
‫من الجيد أن كلانا طباخين‬
Wait a second!
‫مهلًا!‬
Is that your share?!
‫أتلك حصتك أنت؟!‬
It's at least three times bigger than mine!
‫إنها ضخمة، أكبر من حصتي بأضعاف!‬
Of course it is.
‫بالطبع‬
I'm an adult.
‫فأنا رجل بالغ‬
My stomach is larger than yours.
‫تحتاج معدتي لطعام أكثر منك‬
Be grateful I'm even sharing the food with you.
‫يجدر بك أن تكون ممتنًا لأنني تشاركت طعامًا معك‬
Don't expect any pity from me.
‫لا تتأمل أية شفقة مني‬
You old fart!
‫عجوز لعين!‬
You watch the other side of the sea.
‫انتبه للجانب الآخر من البحر‬
Let me know as soon as you see a ship.
‫أعلمني بمجرد رؤيتك لسفينة‬
Until then, no contact. It's a waste of energy.
‫ولحينها لن نتواصل إطلاقًا، لأنها مجرد إضاعة للطاقة‬
Good luck.
‫حظًّا سعيدًا‬
That old fart!
‫عجوز لعين!‬
I won't talk to him even if I see a ship.
‫لن أعلمه حتى إن رأيت سفينة‬
It'll be fine.
‫سأكون بخير‬
I have five days worth of food.
‫لدي مؤونة خمسة أيام‬
That's definitely enough time for a ship or two to pass by.
‫قد تمر سفينة أو سفينتين خلال هذا الوقت‬
But just in case...
‫لكن من باب الاحتياط...‬
I'll make it last twenty days.
‫سأقسمها لعشرين يومًا‬
That has to be enough time to see a passing ship.
‫ستمر سفينة خلال هذا الوقت حتمًا‬
It'll be all right. I'll definitely survive.
‫سأكون بخير، سأنجو بكل تأكيد‬
It's easy!
‫هذا أمر هين!‬
No ship passed by today.
‫لم تمر أي سفينة اليوم‬
No problem. I'll just be patient for a few more days.
‫لا بأس، عليّ الصبر لبضعة أيام وحسب‬
I don't wanna die...
‫لا أريد الموت...‬
My last loaf of bread.
‫هذه آخر قطعة خبز...‬
It's kind of moldy...
‫وقد نال منها العفن...‬
You need to stop eating the customers' leftovers.
‫كفوا عن أكل بقايا الزبائن‬
Some of the food I threw out earlier looked gross.
‫رميتُ الطعام الذي بدا فاسدًا قبل قليل‬
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
‫لمَ لا تتناول بعضه أيضًا؟‬
I don't want it!
‫لا أريد!‬
My last loaf of bread...!
‫قطعة الخبز الأخيرة...‬
I wonder if that old fart...
‫أتساءل إن كان ذلك العجوز اللعين...‬
kicked the bucket yet...
‫ميتًا الآن...‬
He's still alive...?
‫ما زال حيًّا...‬
And look at all his food!
‫ولديه طعام أيضًا...‬
He still has so much!
‫حتى أنه كثير...‬
There's that much food!
‫هنالك طعام بذلك القدر!‬
I'll take it no matter what.
‫سأسرقه مهما كلف الأمر‬
It was all his fault to begin with!
‫كل هذا خطؤه أصلًا!‬
I want to live!
‫أريد أن أعيش!‬
What are you doing over here, little eggplant?
‫ما غايتكَ من المجيء أيها الشقي الصغير؟‬
Did you see a ship or something?
‫أرأيتَ سفينة؟‬
I came to steal your food.
‫أتيتُ لأسرق طعامك‬
If you think you can kill me, go ahead.
‫إن أردتَ قتلي فتفضل‬
I'll die of starvation anyway.
‫سأموت إن لم آكل على أي حال‬
All this food to yourself...!
‫طعامٌ كثيرٌ لك وحدك...‬
Weren't we going to stay out of contact with each other until we saw a ship?
‫ألم أخبرك ألا نتواصل إلى أن نرى سفينة؟‬
Why?
‫لماذا؟‬
This is all treasure...
‫إنه كنز فحسب...‬
Isn't it odd that we can't eat despite having so much money?
‫لا طعام لدينا رغم كل هذا المال، عُجَابٌ أمرنا‬
Hey...
‫مهلًا...‬
This bag is filled with treasure...
‫كان الكيس كنز فحسب...‬
What the hell?!
‫ما هذا؟! ما معنى هذا؟!‬
Where's your food?
‫أين طعامك؟‬
You haven't eaten this whole time?!
‫ألم تأكل من حينها؟‬
Hey! Say something!
‫ويحك، قل شيئًا!‬
What happened to your leg?
‫ماذا حدث لساقك؟‬
And what about the food? Did you give it all to me?!
‫ماذا عن الطعام؟ هل أعطيتني كله؟‬
That's right.
‫أجل‬
Without your leg, doesn't that mean your days as a pirate are over?!
‫دون تلك الساق، لن تستطيع أن ترجع للقرصنة!‬
That goes without saying.
‫فعلًا...‬
Why, though?!
‫لماذا؟ لم أطلب مساعدتك!‬
There's no reason for you to be kind to me!
‫لا أتذكر سببًا يدعوك لأن تتصرف بلطافة معي!‬
So why...?
‫لماذا؟‬
Why'd you do it?!
‫لماذا فعلتَ ذلك؟!‬
Because you...
‫لأن...‬
Because you and I share a dream.
‫لأن حلمي وحلمك سيان‬
The All Blue...
‫الأزرق الكامل...‬
But...
‫لكن...‬
even your men said it doesn't exist.
‫حتى رفاقك قالوا أن لا وجود له‬
But it does!
‫إنه موجود!‬
When the time comes, head to the Grand Line.
‫اتجه صوب الغراند لاين يومًا‬
You'll surely find the All Blue there.
‫الأزرق الكامل موجود فيه حتمًا‬
As you pointed out, my pirating days are over,
‫كما ترى، ما عاد بوسعي العودة للقرصنة،‬
so that's why it'll be you who goes and finds it.
‫فعليك العثور عليه أنت‬
H-Hey! Geezer, don't die!
‫مهلًا، لا تمت أيها العجوز!‬
Don't you be selfish and die on me!
‫لا تفعل ما يحلو لك ولا تمت كما يحلو لك!‬
I wonder how many people have died cursing the sea...
‫أتساءل كم قد ماتوا وهم يلعنون البحر الشاسع...‬
I've experienced crises like this where I was starving.
‫سبق وواجهت أزمات حيث لم أجد طعامًا‬
And each time, I wished...
‫وفي كل مرة كنتُ أتمنى...‬
that there was a restaurant in the middle of the sea.
‫لو كان هنالك مطعم في عرض البحر...‬
A restaurant?
‫مطعم؟‬
Yeah. I was thinking that if I could leave this place alive,
‫أجل، إن عبرت هذه الأزمة بسلامة ففي بالي...‬
I'd build a restaurant and dedicate the rest of my life to it.
‫أن أبني مطعمًا كآخر أهداف حياتي...‬
Alright! I'll help you do just that!
‫سأساعدك في هذا إذًا‬
So don't die!
‫لذلك فلا تمت!‬
A weak little eggplant like you couldn't possibly help!
‫ذلك محالٌ على شقي صغير ضعيف مثلك!‬
Then I'll get stronger!
‫سأصبح أقوى أيضًا!‬
So... don't die!
‫لذلك... لا تمت!‬
Hey!
‫إلى هنا!‬
Help!
‫ساعدونا!‬
You gotta help him!
‫ساعدوا...‬
Please help the old fart!
‫ساعدوا العجوز اللعين!‬
Hey!
‫هنا!‬
The old fart...
‫العجوز اللعين...‬
gave up his leg so that I could live.
‫تخلى عن ساقه لأعيش‬
I can't...
‫أنا لا أستطيع...‬
I can't repay the old fart for his kindness unless I risk my life for him, too!
‫أنا لا أستطيع رد جميل العجوز اللعين...‬
Why are you getting up... Sanji?!
‫لماذا تقف يا سانجي-سان؟‬
I'm getting up to keep this place a restaurant for just a moment longer.
‫لكي يبقى هذا المكان مطعمًا لأطول فترة ممكنة‬
Does that asshole have a death wish?!
‫ذلك الوغد... أيودّ التسبب في مقتله؟‬
Damn brat...!
‫شقي لعين!‬
You put it so elegantly for us.
‫يا للباقة هذه الجملة‬
But this restaurant is closing shop,
‫لكن هذا المطعم سيُغلق...‬
and it will henceforth be a pirate ship!
‫وسيصير سفينة قراصنة!‬
Stop it, you idiot!
‫توقف أيها الغبي!‬
Keep your hands off of them!
‫أبعد يديك عنه‬
What's he about to do?
‫ماذا الذي يحاول فعله؟‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬ ‫فاكهة المطاط‬
Battle Axe!
‫أوغن‬ ‫فأس المعركة‬
As a kid, I had a dream of a dazzling treasure
‫عِندما كُنتُ طفلاً صغيرًا،‬
I had a map in my head that I knew would lead me
‫كانت لديَّ رؤيا عن خريطة كنز‬
Charted a course all on my own, so nobody would beat me
‫ولطالما بحثت عن ذلك المكان العجيب‬
The promised land was in my hand, drew a line in the sand
‫قبل أن يهزمني شخصٌ ما ويسبقني إليه‬
My one ambition's slipping right through my hands
‫إذا كانَ العالم سيتغيّر‬
But if the world ever changes I'll call out your name
‫قبل أن أتمكن من تحقيق حُلمي‬
We could return to a time when our lives were still the same
‫في تلك الحال ارجع بالزمن للوقت الذي لم أعلم به عن شيء‬
Take me to the place where memories remain
‫حتّى لا تتلاشى ذكرياتي‬